
1. What is Semantic HTML? 
1. Semantic HTML is used to explain different parts of a webpage.
2. What is HTML used for? 
2. HTML is basically a blueprint to a webpage.
3. What is an attribute and where do we put it? 
3. attributes are changeble components that can be set to different values. opening tags
4. What is the h1 tag used for? How many times should I use it on a page?
4. h1 is used for the main title of a webpage. Only once per page.
5. Name two tags that have required attributes
5.href and src
6. What do we put in the head of our HTML document? 
6. <header>
7. What is an id? 
7. id is an attribute used to specify an element.
8. What elements can I add an id to? 
8. h1, h2, p, body,     
9. How many times can I use the same id on a page? 
9. only once.
10. What is a class? 
10. class is an attribute used to point to a specific element.
11. What elements can I add a class to? 
11. <div> and <span>.
12. How many times can I use the same class on a page?
12. As many as needed.
13. How do I get my link to open in a new tab?
13. By using href, target and rel.
14. What is the alt attribute in the image tag used for? 
14. Alt uses a text description to an image on a web page.
15. How do I reference an id?
15. a hashtag "#"
16. What is the difference between a section and a div
16. section is used to group the content inside section while div only has meaning in a class attribute.
17. What is CSS used for? 
17. CSS is used for cosmetic reasons
18. How to we select an element? Example - every h2 on the page
18. h2 {}
19. What is the difference between a class and an id? - Give me an example of when I might use each one
19.class: #main {
    background: #000;
    border: 1px solid #AAAAAA;
    padding: 10px;
    color: #fff;
    width: 100px;
}
quote> <div id="main">
    Welcome
</div>
20. How do we select classes in CSS?
20. a period then the class name
21. How do we select a p element with a single class of “human””?
21. p.human {}
22. What is a parent child selector? When would this be useful? 
22. It selects all children under the parent element. When you trying to change all children under a parent. 
23. How do you select all links within a div with the class of sidebar?
23. $(div.sidebar)
24. What is a pseudo selector?
24. CSS selector with a colon after. a:hover
25. What do we use the change the spacing between lines?
25. line-height
26. What do we use to change the spacing between letters?
26. letter-spacing
27. What do we use to to change everything to CAPITALS? lowercase? Capitalize? 
27. text-transform: (capital)(lowercase)(capitalize)
28. How do I add a 1px border around my div that is dotted and black?
28. div.class {
28. div.class { border: 1px dotted #000000
29. How do I select everything on the page? 
29. function SelectAll
30. How do I write a comment in CSS?
30. /*""*/     
31. How do I find out what file I am in, when I am using the command line? 
31. ls
32. Using the command line - how do I see a list of files/folders in my current folder?
32. ls -a
33. How do I remove a file via the command line? Why do I have to be careful with this?
34. Why should I use version control?
34. To prevent multiple users cluttering the main branch.
35. How often should I commit to github?
35. Often
36. What is the command we would use to push our repo up to github?
36. git push -u
37. Walk me through Lambda's git flow. 
37. Git clone > git pull > git clone > cd > git checkout > git add > git commit > git push

